<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Music Library</string>
    <string name="now_playing">Now Playing Screen Icon</string>
    <string name="rewind">Previous Song Icon</string>
    <string name="play">Play Song Icon</string>
    <string name="fastforward">Next Song Icon</string>
    <string name="albums">Albums</string>
    <string name="playlists">Playlists</string>
    <string name="artists">Artists</string>
    <string name="songs">Songs</string>
    <string name="genres">Genres</string>
    <string name="playBarDummyText">Artist and Song Details</string>
    <string name="albumsText">This is the starting page of the app and will have a vertical scrolled tiled view of the albums stored on the device.
        If any of the album tiles are selected then this will navigate to the album page. All of the albums pages will have the same structure but will call
        different source data depending on the user selection. The user can also select one of the buttons at the top of the screen to change the filter
        type to something more suitable and this will re-organise the music display</string>
    <string name="playlistsText">This will have the same layout and navigation as the Albums page but organised by user Playlists instead. There will
        be a button to a new screen to create a new playlist and assign all of the required details for the new playlist</string>
    <string name="artistsText">This will have the same layout and navigation as the Albums page but organised by Artist name</string>
    <string name="songsText">This will have the same layout and navigation as the Albums page but organised by Song name</string>
    <string name="genresText">This will have the same layout and navigation as the Albums page but organised by Genre</string>
    <string name="nowPlayingText">Screen will contain Album cover / Playlist Image / Artist Image etc… along with a scrolling view below of the tracks in the
        list for the user to select the track that they want to listen to. There will also be a shuffle button to randomise the play along with another button
        that will select a single \'run through\' of the list of an infinite repeat until the user intervenes. The bar at the bottom has been modified to re-use
        the icons from the previous screen to keep some consistancy while changing due to the different screen layout.</string>

</resources>
